This place is gonna collapse!
ที่นี่กำลังจะพังลงมาแล้ว!
It's been a while since we flew like this together
เราไม่ได้บินด้วยกันแบบนี้มานานแล้วนะ
Huh, Dvalin?
Dvalin
Just now... Why...
เมื่อกี้...ทำไม...
Why did you not ask me to protect you like the last time?
ทำไมถึงไม่สั่งให้ข้า "ปกป้อง" ท่าน
Me not wanting you to listen to the Abyss Order
ฉันไม่อยากให้เธอฟังพวก Abyss Order อีก
Doesn't mean that you have to listen to me
แต่ก็ไม่ใช่ว่าเธอจะต้องฟังฉันนะ Dvalin
Freedom, if demanded of you by an archon
คำสั่งของเทพที่ให้เธอมี "อิสระ"
Is really no freedom at all
ฟังดู "ไม่อิสระ" เท่าไหร่เลยนะ
Is this... the power of the Anemo Archon?
นี่คือ...พลังของเทพแห่งลมเหรอ?
But I am no longer part of the Four Winds
แต่ข้าไม่ได้เป็น "สี่วายุ" อีกต่อไปแล้ว...
Even if that's so
แม้ไม่ใช่ตัวตนนั้นแล้ว
You still protected us regardless
ยังไงเธอก็จะยังปกป้องเราอยู่ดีรึเปล่า?
Now, spread your wings of freedom
จากนี้ไป ด้วยพรแห่งข้า
And go with my blessing
จงกางปีกออก แล้วโบยบินไปด้วยอิสรภาพ
And so, the Stormterror threat was quelled
ภัยพิบัติมังกรของ Mondstadt สิ้นสุดลงแล้ว
I clarified the misunderstanding to the citizens of Mondstadt
ฉันจะชี้แจงความเข้าใจผิดต่อสาธารณชนในนามของอัศวิน
And let them know that they are safe
และแจ้งว่าเหตุการณ์ได้จบลงแล้ว
To them it seems
จากมุมมองของประชาชนทั่วไป
Stormterror attacked Mondstadt out of nowhere
"มังกรวายุ" ได้เข้าโจมตีเมือง Mondstadt
And then vanished just as quickly
และหายตัวไปโดยไม่เหลือร่องรอย
However, winds change their course
แต่อย่างไร สายลมก็จะเปลี่ยนทิศไปเสมอ
Someday
ในสักวันหนึ่ง